# Mary Ann Denman | UX Designer

As a User Experience Designer with a background in nursing and project management, I solve problems through my application of empathy. I design user-centered experiences that are engaging and accessible to provide an inclusive environment that achieves the required business goals while still allowing people to have dignity and feel respected. Personally, I enjoy volunteering and participating in innovative projects that support the needs of local community.

Seattle, WA (770) 335-5602 maryann.n.denman@gmail.com maryanndenman.com linkedin.com/in/maryanndenman github.com/nunezmei

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### UX Design Immersive Student - General Assembly - Seattle, WA

OCTOBER 2017 - PRESENT

10 week full-time immersive program covering more than 60 hours/week class instruction and project work.

### UX Designer - StringClub - Seattle, WA

APRIL 2017 - PRESENT

Work through user experience for StringClub site, specifically the instrument and user profile pages; helped to define application of Google material design.

### Director - Kusog Software, Inc. - Atlanta, GA

MAY 2012 - PRESENT

Full life-cycle recruiting of contract and temp-to-hire resources for the IT industry.

### 2005-2011

Cebu, Philippines

Director - Syrinx, Inc

Registered Nurse OPD-ER - Seamen's Hospital Cebu AMOSUP

### **EDUCATION**

## **General Assembly -** Seattle,WA-UX Design Immersive

OCTOBER 2017 - JANUARY 2018

# **Cebu Normal University – College of Nursing** – Cebu, Philippines – *B.S. Nursing*

JUNE 2000 - March 2004

### **CERTIFICATION**

### **REGISTERED NURSE-JULY 2004-PRESENT**

Philippine Professional Regulation Commission - Board of Nursing

### **SKILLS**

User Interviews, Competitive Analysis, Heuristic Evaluation, Affinity Diagrams, Personas, Sketching, Wireframing, User Flows, User Scenarios, Rapid Prototyping, Usability Testing

Project Management, Recruiting, Strategic Planning, Compassion, Calm Under Pressure, Patience

HTML5, CSS3

#### **TOOLS**

Sketch, InVision, OmniGraffle, Pop, Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Illustrator, Visual Studio Code

# AFFILIATIONS/COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

Member - IxDA Seattle,WA AUGUST 2017-PRESENT

Supported Living Activities Volunteer - Horizon House Seattle, WA OCTOBER 2015-PRESENT

Parent Volunteer - Boy Scouts of America Cumming, GA & Seattle, WA SEPTEMBER 2014-PRESENT

### **LANGUAGES**

Cebuano-Fluent Level Tagalog-Fluent Level English- Business Level